Hercules Formation, abort mission.
Negative. We can't return without Hyena 2.
Hercules 1, it is too risky.
There are Stingers out there, Hercules.
Nishi is alone.
I won't come back until I've found him.
Deviating from your planned mission.
Stinger spotted.
Chief, there's some good news.
We have shot down
an Indian Air Force jet in Kargil.
Excellent.
Now let's see
how many more pilots the Indian Air Force
will send to their deaths.
For the last 52 years,
the India-Pakistan border
has been engulfed by war,
suspicion, and mistrust.
And last year, when the two countries
conducted nuclear tests,
this mistrust reached its peak.
It was called the most dangerous event
in the world after World War II.
But just seven months later,
Prime Minister Atal Bihari Vajpayee
accepted Nawaz Sharif's invitation,
and announced the historic
Lahore Bus Yatra.
Now the question is,
"Will the defense forces of both countries
be able to trust this peace?"
Gentlemen, peace or no peace.
This year too, the Western Air Command's
war game exercise
will take place as scheduled.
Like every year,
this will be a test of your flying skills,
alertness, innovation,
and bravery.
This year too, all the squadrons
will be split into two teams.
Red Land and Blue Land.
But this year,
for the first time,
in Blue Land,
a Photo Recce Squadron
will also be involved.
Golden Arrows,
led by Wing Commander Tony Dhanoa,
who will conduct reconnaissance
for the bomb squadron Wolfpack,
identify targets,
and assess post-strike damage.
In the next month,
there will be five operational rounds,
then the semi-finals,
and finals.
Any questions?
No, sir!
Gentlemen, before this exercise,
I asked you all,
"How will you ensure
your squadrons are war-ready?"
And I have received your requirements.
Jammer pods,
self-defense system,
advanced flying simulators.
And someone even asked
for night-vision goggles.
But, Tony,
you haven't asked for a thing.
Sir, in my squadron,
I have some of the youngest fighter pilots
of the Western Air Command.
They're academy-trained,
but it's their first time
flying the MiG-21 operationally.
Sir, you and I both know
MiG-21 has the fastest take-off
and landing speed in the world.
Before they become war-ready,
I want my boys to be MiG-ready.
And for that, we don't need any equipment.
We need a good coach.
And who is this coach?
Squadron Leader Ajay Ahuja.
I can't think of a better name than him
to turn my boys into men.
Sorry, Alka.
We need to keep moving because of me.
"Sorry"?
I was about to say thank you.
"Thank you," why?
For so many new sarees.
At a new posting,
even old sarees become new.
Hey, champion.
Come on, tell me.
Fourteen eights are?
-One, one, two.
-Too slow.
Do you want to become
a fighter pilot or not?
A fighter pilot has to solve math problems
in a second.
1700 hours. Be ready.
There's an even bigger swimming pool here.
Okay, Dad.
-Bye.
You have become a flight commander,
at least buy a decent bike.
I have 16 MiGs, ma'am.
If the Flight Commander rides in
on a scooter from the Stone Age,
what impression will it make on the boys?
Sir, why is everyone
obsessed with my scooter?
In any case, if you come to think of it,
our MiGs are older than my scooter.
Right, Tony sir?
You and your twisted logic.
Come here. Come.
Welcome to Golden Arrows.
-Good to see you again, Ahuja.
-Thank you, sir.
Oh, wow.
Annual war game exercise, sir.
Semi-finals.
It's time for the boys
to meet their new coach.
As the dedicated photo recce squadron,
our job is to approach the target,
fly low and take photos.
Then enlarge these photos
and share the exact strike coordinates
with the bombing squadron.
As soon as you cross this make-shift LoC,
the timer will start.
Forty-five seconds.
If you haven't returned within 45 seconds,
Red Land's surface-to-air missiles
will lock on to you,
and for all practical purposes,
you're dead,
and we'll lose points.
And that cannot happen.
-Jai Hind, sir.
-Jai Hind.
At ease, Arrows.
I want you
to meet your new flight commander.
Squadron Leader Ajay Ahuja.
Ajay was supposed to join us tomorrow.
But I guess he was dying to see you guys.
What do you think our strategy should be?
The enemy will have missiles, sir.
We must fly the mission in radio silence.
I am not talking about that mission.
I'm talking about the India-Pakistan
peace summit on 19th February.
For the first time in 52 years,
our prime minister
will be going to Pakistan by road.
What are your thoughts
about this bus trip?
I think this is a good step, sir.
Both have nuclear weapons.
It's very important
to find a permanent solution.
Sir, a permanent solution is impossible.
-Tensions may subside a little, that's it.
-How?
Mistake.
This is a big mistake, sir.
A country like Pakistan cannot be trusted.
Peace is also necessary
between India and Pakistan.
The other country should also have
the same intention, right, Baldy?
Ahuja, what do you think?
Sir, I don't think about all this.
Exactly!
You shouldn't even think about it.
Politics is not the Air Force's concern.
We are razor blades.
We are trained to cut,
not to think about all this.
We are 17 points behind.
If you don't get 20 points
in the semi-finals,
no matter how many
fancy maneuvers you do,
Red land will end up winning.
Chou.
Boys for the mission?
Dhali and Goofy.
Boys,
this is the closest you will get
to experiencing war.
It's a war you've never lost, sir.
And I will not lose this time either.
Go get me those points.
-Yes, sir.
Long live Pakistan, sir.
Long live.
Sir, what brings you here?
The World Cup is around the corner,
so I thought I'd give the players
a little encouragement.
Anyway, there's hardly any difference
between players and soldiers.
We are always fighting for the next war.
Very true, sir.
Junaid was six years old.
Even then he wanted
to become a fast bowler.
Sir, you still remember?
Of course, Tauqir.
Inshallah, he will soon play
for Pakistan's cricket team too.
How, sir? With Younis, Akhtar…
Akram and all in the mix,
it is difficult, sir.
Tauqir sahib,
when his own father
is set to become the chairman
of the Pakistan Cricket Board,
what difficulty will he face?
Sir?
A new PCB chairman
will be elected in December.
For this post, who could be better than
the Pakistan Army's star sportsperson?
Sir, the Pakistan team
is a big responsibility.
Are you afraid to take on responsibility?
No, sir.
Can you get Pakistan another World Cup?
I will try, sir.
Then surely you'll also get Kashmir
for Pakistan?
Kashmir, sir?
Every year, the armies of both countries
descend from
the snowy mountain peaks of Kashmir,
as per the Simla Agreement.
And as DGMO, it is your office
that gives these orders, right?
Right, sir.
But this time,
our soldiers will not descend.
But, sir, this is a violation
of the Simla Agreement--
This is also
a direct violation of the LoC.
Because this time,
our soldiers will go forward.
To capture all those posts across the LoC
that India will have vacated,
honoring the agreement.
Especially those posts
from where India's National Highway 1
will be in our direct line of sight.
But, sir,
Mian sahib is about to begin
peace talks with India.
So?
Pardon me, sir.
Is the Prime Minister aware
of this operation?
It's an army operation, General Zia.
What is the need for Mian sahib in this?
Are the posters for the peace talks ready?
Sir, the layout is ready.
Is the meeting with
Faiz sahib's daughter fixed?
No, sir. He's--
Vajpayee sahib is a great admirer of Faiz.
This should be looked into on priority.
Yes, sir.
Sir, your father's asking for you.
The cabinet has been waiting for a while.
This is filled with mistakes.
Mr. Aqil,
Vajpayee sahib will be
the first Indian prime minister
to set foot in Minar-e-Pakistan.
Understand the significance
of these talks.
-Okay, I'll come.
-Yes, sir.
Please be seated, everyone.
So, what is the agenda
for today's meeting?
-The peace talks only, sir.
-Really?
Our suggestion is that during the talks,
we propose the Chenab River
as the new Line of Control.
This…
The LoC will be like this,
visible even from the moon.
We've talked about this before,
haven't we?
India will never accept this
80-20 division in Pakistan's favor.
Sir,
the Chenab River evenly divides the Hindu
and Muslim populations of Kashmir.
-It's the ideal solution to the conflict.
-Aziz sahib.
I'm the one
speaking to Vajpayee sahib every day.
He will never agree to this.
Nawaz…
By all means, do keep up
your friendly chats with him.
But in the "real" negotiations,
follow Aziz sahib's lead.
When it comes to diplomatic talks,
he has far more experience than all of us.
Yes, Abba ji.
Should we move on to India's draft, sir?
What is your opinion on this, Aziz sahib?
Sir, the Chief has appointed his loyalists
to all key army positions.
So?
Sir, our political history shows that,
whenever the army has expanded its reach,
the outcome has not been good.
Butt sahib, I bypassed three seniors
and made him Army Chief.
Now, if he wants to savor the feeling
of being chief, let him.
How does it matter?
Sir, this is a matter of border positions.
If the chief tries anything reckless
in the valley,
the ISI's long-term Kashmir plan
could be put at risk.
As for me, it's my job to warn you, sir.
Yes, of course.
And my job is to tell the difference.
You focus on ISI operations,
not on General Musharraf.
The new flight commander
isn't exactly giving off commander vibes.
You never judge a jet's power
by the size of its body, Goofy.
Getting a feeling from the mission?
Bad weather above,
anti-aircraft guns below.
There is danger everywhere.
Of course I'm feeling good about it
Perfect.
Happy landings, Goofy.
Trident taxy via link Alpha Runway
2-7-QNH-1-0-0-2.
Link Alpha, Runway 2-7-1-0-0-2, copied.
Trident in sequence.
Trident sequence, monitored.
Sir.
Vanguard Control,
Trident Formation, ready to take off.
These rolls were part of the briefing?
Sir, that's Flying Officer Dhaliwal.
Very talented.
And a bit of a show-off too, sir.
Can we go to the ops room?
Sure, sir.
Sir, would you be attending
the debrief today?
On my first day?
-I think today I'll just observe?
-Right, sir.
Sir, message from Met Department.
"Heavy cloud patch in Trident's route."
-Sir?
-Safety first, always.
Break RT silence. Alert them.
Trident, Vanguard Control.
Exercise caution
for large cloud build up.
There's heavy patch coming your way--
RT silence, Khan.
Whatever it is, I will handle it.
Trident 2, Vanguard Control.
Exercise caution
for large cloud buildup in sector.
Zero-four-zero, 30 kilometers.
Roger. Copy, Trident 2.
RT silence, Goofy.
Do you want to gossip on channel 2?
Dhali, what are you doing, man?
There's a cloud alert.
Right now we're up in the air,
aren't we, Goofy?
So just follow my lead.
This is the semi-final mission.
No matter what,
we will complete it on time.
Vanguard Control, Trident 2,
leader is not responding.
Going ahead as planned.
Trident Formation,
lost Joy on you.
Trident Formation, confirm monitored.
Shit!
Dhali!
Trident Formation, confirm ops normal.
Affirmative. Heading to the party.
Close shave, boys.
But the real mission starts now.
And you have only 45 seconds.
Go get those points.
Trident Formation is approaching target.
Mission completed.
Heading back to base.
Sir, Trident Formation
is heading back to base.
I changed my mind, Chou.
I… will attend the debriefing.
-Sergeant, take the camera to the PIC.
-Sir.
Are you okay?
That was a bit much, don't you think?
You felt good about it, didn't you?
Goofy, why did you
follow instead of aborting the mission?
Sir, the leader asked me to follow,
so there was no option to abort.
Textbook wingman call.
Well done.
And you? Ground orders were clear.
So why did you
take the risk of flying into the clouds?
For 20 mission points, sir.
The risk of collision for both pilots
was very high during cloud flying.
Did you factor that in?
Sir, we've flown together for a year.
We completely trust each other, sir.
And, suppose,
while flying in the clouds,
you became disoriented?
We could've easily reoriented, sir.
Only our squadron
has a global positioning system.
Grounded.
For one week.
No sorties.
Sorry, sir?
For a week,
you will only perform ground duties.
Bird clearance, paperwork…
You'll interpret photos
from the other pilots' sorties.
Pardon me, sir. But why?
The mission needed to be completed,
and I only took a calculated risk.
Sir, if we didn't do this,
we would have lost, and the entire blame
would have fallen on Golden Arrows.
It's as simple as that, sir.
And, there was no other way, sir.
Does everyone feel the same,
that
there was no other way?
There was, sir.
There was a way.
Go on, Baldy. Explain.
Sir, dogleg maneuver.
You could have gone around the cloud.
And the time
that would have gone into rerouting?
Two minutes at the most.
The length of the cloud
was ten kilometers.
And a detour around the clouds…
that's 20 kilometers.
What about the extra fuel
the detour would've cost?
Sir, at a speed of 800 kmph,
we probably used way more fuel
handling the cloud turbulence
than the extra amount needed
to cover that ten-kilometer difference.
I think dogleg was a safer
and more efficient option.
Clearly, what is safe for me
is dangerous
for our "professor sahib" here.
And it's fine. Every pilot
has their own risk-taking capability--
So, you agree.
That there was another way.
Sir, in that moment,
it was just me up in the air.
You weren't there and nor was he.
And if it were wartime, sir,
would we still abort--
Grounded for two weeks, Dhaliwal.
Let's save the risk for a real war.
There is no war going on right now.
As-salamu alaykum, Chief.
I have an urgent update to give.
Lieutenant General Aziz
and Lieutenant General Mahmud
are both on the line.
Tell me.
Sir, as per the plan,
soldiers from our 12NLI
have captured eight vacant Indian posts.
But as they moved forward,
they found many more hidden posts
we were not even aware of.
It's clear that India
is guarding NH1 like a fortress.
And now that
India is honoring the agreement
and stepping down from all these posts,
we should take full advantage
of this situation.
I think we should take them all, sir.
Hassan, to hold posts
across such a vast area,
we will have to cancel the winter holidays
of 3,000 to 4,000 soldiers.
We're already violating
the Simla Agreement
by crossing the LoC in winter.
Capturing 200 square kilometers of area
would be a major invasion.
General Mahmud, do you set out
to capture Kashmir every day?
No, sir.
So, you'll never get
a better opportunity than this.
-General Hassan.
-Yes, sir.
Start preparing to capture
all those posts.
Not even in their wildest dreams
would they imagine
we could do something like this.
In this operation, our audacity
will be our greatest strength.
Start making a list of supplies.
I'm sending Tauqir Zia to you.
-Long live Pakistan.
-Long live Pakistan, sir.
Dhali. I have some good news.
The bombing squadron destroyed
Red Land's comms base.
And we won the semi-finals.
-I know.
-That's true.
But I got my next posting.
Mirage Squadron.
Mir--
Straight from Maruti to Ferrari.
Congratulations, Sangy.
Hopefully, there's no flight commander
there who punishes risk-taking.
Let it go, Dhali.
You won us the semi-finals, man.
Let's celebrate that today.
Let's go. Drinks are on me tonight.
No, man. Have fun.
I'm not in the mood. Thank you.
It is unfair.
Let's all talk to him together.
Let's see what Ahuja sir says.
Yes, let's see.
He's the Flight Commander.
He'll do whatever he wants,
nobody can say a thing.
So what if he's the flight commander?
We're bachelors too!
Maybe we can't reason with him,
but we can definitely mess with him.
Let's go.
Where is Professor sahib?
He'll be where he is every evening.
Okay. Let's go then!
Bala, do you love me or not?
What kind of question is that?
Of course I do.
So, will you elope with me?
Madhavi, I haven't even become
a flight lieutenant yet.
My training is still going on.
Right now,
I don't think it's the right time.
There's a lot of pressure at home.
Please try to understand.
Bouncing?
You guys go.
We are not asking.
Madhavi, I will call you in an hour.
Hello?
It got cut.
-Hello, ma'am.
Aren't you guys quite late?
In the previous squadron,
the bachelors had come to bounce
on the second day itself.
Your team has arrived.
Finally.
Welcome home, boys.
I don't drink.
But I get others drunk.
This bar is all yours. Help yourself.
You're in some form, huh, Dhali?
-It's my second, man. It's his seventh.
-It's your seventh?
It's all free while bouncing, no?
So he's drinking his heart's fill!
Doesn't want to pay for his drinks!
Let's go.
Start chopping.
We will make my special dish.
You want to eat, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Then get started.
What are you looking at?
This house belongs to Alka ma'am.
I just live here.
Come on.
I'll chop the carrots.
I'll chop the potatoes.
Bro, it feels like
coming here to bounce has backfired.
Honestly, these two seem
way more in sync than us.
What's all this whispering?
If you wanted to talk to each other,
why did you come here to bounce?
Let's all hear it, come on.
Sir, actually, Max was asking
about the war game exercise finals--
Bouncing rule number one in this house,
there will be no talk of flying.
-No talk of flying, bro.
-There won't be.
-Sir.
-Thank you, Sangy.
But, ma'am, this is a very unfair rule.
If this was a rule in my house,
I would never have become a fighter pilot.
This conversation is allowed.
Rajendra Dhaliwal, ma'am, my father…
He was also in the Air Force.
Ground duty officer.
And my mother was an amazing cook.
So, all the fighter pilots used to come
to bounce at our house.
Growing up listening
to all their flying stories,
one day I got bitten by the bug.
Where is Dad posted now?
-He's retired.
Wing Commander Dhaliwal.
'69 batch.
Disciplined officer.
-I'd met him briefly in Tezpur.
-Hey, one minute.
Ahuja sir has a file on everyone.
But I don't know anything.
So how did the rest of you catch this bug?
-Yes?
-Sangy.
Ma'am, where I come from, the only way
to get out of town is to join the army.
My father, my grandfather,
both were in the army.
But neither of them could fight in a war.
So, I'm just trying to pay off that debt.
Ma'am, he doesn't drink much, so he's
always caught between debt and duty.
Ma'am, when you said "special,"
I had something else in mind.
I never imagined pulao could be so good.
What's in it?
Thank you so much for the food, ma'am.
But I have to leave now.
I have an urgent call to make.
Well, who's going to wash the dishes?
Forgotten the tradition?
By the way, Baldy,
you can call from here too.
-We have an STD connection.
-Yes, do it.
Sir, he wants to make
a private call from a public booth.
You can go, Baldy.
Dhali, you can do
Baldy's share of the dishes.
Yes. Sure, ma'am.
But who is she, Professor sahib?
You're ditching
the entire squadron for her.
No one, Dhali.
I have an urgent family call.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you, sir. Thank you, ma'am.
But what family emergency came up?
Dhali, wallet.
I'm just taking out
her contact for everyone.
There must be
a photo of the person in here.
-I'm just checking, man.
-Don't do it.
-Hey, wait a minute. Here it is. I see it.
-Dhali!
I'll get the first aid kit.
Oh, no, ma'am.
-I'm completely fine. I'm absolutely okay.
-No, you're not.
I am absolutely fine, ma'am.
Sir.
Mian sahib, I can say with certainty
that this fellow is up to no good.
You should not trust him too much.
General.
We were just about to start. Come.
Sir, you called me so urgently.
Is everything all right?
Butt sahib has some concerns.
I thought I'd take this opportunity
to also have breakfast with you.
I've already had breakfast, Mian sahib.
But I'll have some fruit.
Tell me, Butt sahib.
What are the ISI's concerns?
The concern is
why are we cancelling the winter holidays
of thousands of soldiers of the X Corps
and sending them to Skardu?
Such heavy troop movement
along the LoC during peace talks?
It's a bit alarming.
Sir, we have intel that some Mujahideen
are planning to infiltrate the valley
in order to derail the peace talks.
As ISI Chief, perhaps you didn't get
this piece of intel.
Sir, to maintain peace at the border,
many leaves have been canceled.
Many have been deployed along the border.
So this means you are
doing this to protect
the security of the peace talks?
Yes, sir. Of course.
Very thoughtful.
Sir, the army and the government have been
locked in a tug-of-war for a long time.
I want to put an end to this.
I want to show the public
that Rawalpindi and Islamabad
can play on the same pitch, sir.
We can work together.
See, Butt sahib. I told you, didn't I?
There's no need to worry
about General Musharraf.
He is playing on our team.
I am sorry, ma'am. I've double-checked.
Your name is not
on the approved visitor list.
Sir, please just connect me to Bala once…
I mean, put me through
to Flying Officer Bal Reddy.
He'll explain everything to you.
Sorry, madam. An exercise is going on.
Nothing can be done right now.
Then let me talk to the CO.
Tony sir, right?
Sorry, sir.
I had no idea
Madhavi was coming here.
-Chou.
-Sir?
Can she be accommodated
in the VIP guesthouse?
Fully occupied, sir.
Sir…
she can stay with us.
Alka and I will be happy to host Madhavi.
Okay then.
Baldy, you can get back to work.
Yes, sir.
The siren for the war game finals
can go off anytime. We need to be ready.
Our target will be
Red Land's key airbase.
But this time we'll take photos
after the bombing, not before,
to find out
if the bombs hit their target or not.
Battle damage assessment is far more
dangerous than photo recon flying.
Because we won't have
the element of surprise.
Their radars will be waiting for us.
And they'll certainly have
surface-to-air missiles.
So this time, we will try a new strategy.
This strategy will serve us
not only in a war game, but also in war.
If this is the enemy's radar screen…
how many dots will be visible on it?
Sir, six.
Exactly.
Six jets in close formation.
So close that it should appear as
one big dot on the enemy's radar screen.
And the enemy should think
it's a large transport aircraft.
We will fly in close formation
up to the target.
And at the last minute,
we'll break formation and click photos.
And after clicking photos,
before their interceptors arrive,
we will have crossed the mock LoC.
Into friendly skies. Clear?
What's wrong, boys? Too risky?
Dhali, I was going to reinstate you.
-But okay. If you can't, then--
-No. We can, sir.
We will do it.
-Come again?
-We'll do it, sir!
Good.
And, Dhali, this time
you won't be flying with Goofy.
I've shuffled everyone's wingmen.
Check the flying program board.
Baldy, call in position.
I'm at 700, match my speed.
-In position.
-Now maintain position, Baldy.
Sangy joining up. Goofy call in position.
Goofy joining up.
-Teekay joining up.
-Max joining up.
Tridents, Diamond formation is complete.
Let's maintain speed.
Let's not mess it up, guys.
Baldy, too close.
You're falling behind, man.
Sorry, Sangy. Maintaining.
Baldy, it's not a school bus.
Maintain 700.
-Dhali, slow down and match Baldy's speed?
-Negative.
The mission also has to be carried out
at this speed, right?
-Baldy, increase your speed.
-Roger.
Increasing.
Formation stable at 700.
Ready to turn left.
Baldy, be on guard.
Tridents, pan left 0-5-3.
Formation stable at turn.
Accelerate to 750 now!
Baldy, what are you doing?
You're falling behind again.
Baldy, we're not even close to Mach 1!
Maintain 750.
I'm trying.
Dhali, why aren't you listening?
-Let's maintain speed with Baldy.
-Negative. Let's stick to 750.
Everyone, 750 now!
Baldy, what are you doing, man?
We'll collide. Teekay, peel off, now!
-Teekay peeling off!
-Arrows, peel off!
Abort! Abort! Abort!
Come on, guys!
Sit, sit, sit, Please.
What happened?
Why is everyone in such a bad mood?
It was a practice sortie,
not a war exercise mission.
Another round for everyone, please.
Sangy?
We celebrate life
after close calls, don't we?
We do celebrate, sir.
But this call was way too close.
We almost collided.
It was probably the first time
we were flying in a formation of six.
And so, it became a little difficult
to stay in sync with each other.
No, sir. I am to blame for this.
Sir, it was my fault.
I…
I was having trouble
matching Dhali's speed.
Sir, the problem…
was the choice of exercise.
Okay.
Sir, Ahuja sir makes us do
an extremely risky exercise.
Which is fine with me. I'm up for it.
But then,
to suddenly shuffle our wingmen, sir.
How will perfection be achieved, sir?
Suddenly?
When you encounter a technical glitch
in the air, it happens suddenly.
When the decision to eject has to be made,
no one leaves home thinking that
they will have to eject today.
It happens suddenly.
I haven't called Ahuja here
for your routine exercises.
I've called him
so he can prepare you for war.
Because when war breaks out,
even that happens suddenly.
If you guys think of yourselves
as fighter pilots,
then have the courage
to accept a challenge,
and not just complain about it.
We're meant to be razor blades. Right?
-Yes, sir.
Then bloody behave like one.
-Long live Pakistan.
Welcome to Skardu, sir.
Hassan,
what are Mujahideen doing
at this army base?
Come, sir.
I'll explain it to you.
So the Pakistan Army
will now work with Mujahideen?
Do they seem like Mujahideen to you?
Then that's how they'll seem
to the Indians too.
Then, it will also seem to them that
the Pakistan Army has no role in this.
Because we will
only speak to them in Pashto.
But the truth is,
these are not Mujahideen.
They are 2,000 soldiers of our 12 NLI.
-Naara-e-Takbeer!
-Allah-hu-Akbar!
Sir.
You briefed me on eight posts
and 100 soldiers.
The preparations underway in Skardu…
it's no less than a war, sir.
General Zia, you look quite refreshed.
Looks like fresh mountain air
suits you rather well.
General Zia, the more posts we capture,
the more pressure we can put on India.
Undoubtedly, the height advantage
will allow us to take on the Indian Army.
But what if they involve their air force?
We have double-checked
with the German and Russian Air Forces.
In that terrain, at those heights,
no Air Force in the world can operate!
And this is a proven fact.
Sir, still I feel
our soldiers on the peaks
should be armed with Stinger missiles.
"Mujahideen."
Not our soldiers, Mujahideen, General Zia.
Aren't you the DGMO?
Give them the Stingers.
What's the big deal?
Sir, Stinger missiles
are not regular weapons.
For large-scale mobilization,
we will need the PM's approval.
You worry too much, Tauqir.
If we are to snatch Kashmir from India,
we'll have to put in
a little bit of effort, won't we?
When the time comes, I'll get Mian sahib
to sign off on everything.
We have to seize Kashmir.
Subtitle translation by: Ajay Singh